<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<section xml:id="the-terran-terminators">

<title>The Terran Terminators:</title>

<para>In 1982 it seemed likely that <link xlink:href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jim_Henson">Jim Henson</link> would be Earth’s ultimate false prophet.
But Henson was increasingly unhappy: worried about a possible Nuclear Winter,
about Environmental issues, and thinking the Muppets franchise was unpopular
and silly. Moreover, hell holes' liberation [followed by universe forks] happened
at a dazzling rate.</para>

<para><link xl:href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joss_Whedon">Joss Whedon</link> thought to
himself "it is too easy! where's the challenge in that?",
and eventually Henson admitted inferiority to the team of <link xl:href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Samantha_Smith">Samantha Smith</link>, Whedon, (and
<link xl:href="https://buffy.fandom.com/wiki/Buffy_Summers">Buffy Summers</link>?), and was slain
and relieved. If Jim Henson was the new Walt Disney, then Joss Whedon was
poised to be the new Jim Henson.</para>

<para>
<link xl:href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Samantha_Smith">Samantha Smith</link>, a 1972-born American girl and a false prophet, engaged in a snailmail dialogue with the secretary of the USSR. <link xl:href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joss_Whedon">Joss Whedon</link> joined forces with Henson and they both suggested using the <link xlink:href="#terrestrial">terrestrial</link> mass media infrastructure in place for <link xl:href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Muppet_Show">The Muppet Show</link> to air a The Muppet Show special starring her with the ascension mantra. A die roll determined it will have 100% viewership, will be passed verbatim, but there may be a surprise at the end.
</para>

<para>
All the remaining false prophets were avid fans of The Muppet Show, but may have thought it was considered silly and childish among the general public. In actuality, Jim Henson and the muppeteers were multiverse superstars and heroes. The Samantha Smith episode was particularly bizarre featuring a <link xl:href="https://muppet.fandom.com/wiki/Muppet_Labs">Muppet Labs</link> skit where Bunsen and Beaker tested a membrane to enclose a (real!) <link xl:href="https://github.com/shlomif/shlomif-tech-diary/blob/master/hydrogen-bombs-are-likely-an-old-intelligence-hoax.asciidoc">hydrogen bomb</link>; the membrane didn’t work and yet there was only a local sand splash.
</para>

<para>
Eventually, <link xl:href="https://muppet.fandom.com/wiki/Count_von_Count">Count von Count</link>,
a friendly <link xl:href="https://buffyfanfiction.fandom.com/wiki/Selinaverse#Vampires_in_the_Selinaverse">vampire</link>, caused
an ear-screeching noise to be emitted. After Samantha Smith protested and said "you could have killed us", he noted <quote>I couldn’t have killed you. You can never die or feel physical pain for long. Consider yourself slain and free of The-Curse. Your world is what you want it to be. Your imagination is the limit. It’ll be a new technology, that we call 'Neo-Tech'. Now let’s party <quote><link xl:href="https://www.shlomifish.org/humour/Selina-Mandrake/indiv-nodes/vampires-gathering-in-the-hall.xhtml">Jehovah, Jehovah, Jehovah, Jehovah,</link></quote></quote>
</para>

<para>All the remaining false prophets have watched that episode and had ascended. All
the remaining hell holes: <link xl:href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/London">London</link>
or just <link xl:href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/London_Borough_of_Harrow">Harrow</link>
Gush Dan or just Tel Aviv, parts of Austria, Beverly Hills, etc. were plugged and even
became
places of life, love, magic, and youth. <link xlink:href="#zionism">"Zionism"</link>
which transported terrestrial false prophets to places where the two will give birth
to a new false prophet was now impossible.</para>

<section xml:id="slaying-jim-henson">

<title>"Buffy the Vampire Slayer" ( BtVS )</title>

<para>
One should note that Samantha Smith had previously written a funny story titled
"Buffy the Vampire Slayer" that she believed received a lukewarm reception
from her friends. Its original manuscript was later auctioned for
millions of US Dollars.
</para>

</section>

</section>

